pixelsmedia.net 2015-11-18

# Privacy Policy - Web Design and Web Development Company

#### Information collected by us using the various forms on our website

If you would like to enquire about any services offered on our website, you will be asked to provide basic online contact information such as your name, mailing address, e-mail address, and other personal identifying information.

 _Use of Personal Information collected on http://www.pixelsmedia.net_

The information collected is kept strictly confidential by us.

The information collected is solely used to:

  * Contact you in order to respond to your individual needs.
  * To improve customer service
  * To send periodic email campaigns that keep you informed about special offers, upcoming events, new services introduced and pricing. In case you choose not to receive such emails, you can opt out by clicking on the “Unsubscribe” link at the end of any email.
  * To update you on the status of your project and for various other communications while the project is ongoing.

Pixelsmedia Technologies value and respect your privacy and hence we guarantee that the information collected on [http://www.pixelsmedia.net](http://www.pixelsmedia.net/) will not be given, rented, shared or sold to any other third party, unless legally required to do so.

#### Non Disclosure Agreement (NDA) for our Outsource Partners

As outsource partners, we sign Non Disclosure Agreement (NDA) with our clients, which outlines that we do not resell the original artworks or other project information to any third party or give it out to anyone, unless legally required to do so.

#### Your consent to using our website, http://www.pixelsmedia.net

When you provide us with your personal data, you agree to the regulations stipulated under our Privacy Policy.

#### Amendments to the Privacy Policy Statement

Should we change our privacy policy at any point of time, we will update this page on our Website. We recommend and request that you revisit this page from time to time, so that you are aware of any changes that we have made to our Policies.

#### Contacting the website

If you have any questions regarding this privacy statement, please contact us using the information below.

Website: [http://www.pixelsmedia.net](http://www.pixelsmedia.net/)  
E-mail: [admin@pixelsmedia.net](mailto:admin@pixelsmedia.net)  
Phone: 1800-279-1049 (USA) or 033-2357-3330 (INDIA)
